本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
翻译  红豆包 小布拿拿 斯人 Iz  Tiogy
时间轴  深夏桃子   校对&总监  Iz
后期 斯人
还有两天才到万圣节
Two days until trick-or-treating?
这期间让我吃什么啊
What am I supposed to eat until then?
别的食物么
Other food?
我懂  难不成
I know. Like what?
-要我们吃面包吗  -我不确定
- Like, bread? - I don't know
今年还要不要去玩"不给糖就捣蛋"
if I'm gonna go trick-or- treating this year, guys.
大孩子们都会去老墓地玩
All the bigger kids are hanging out at the old cemetery.
小吉米  万圣节你去墓地吗
Hi, Jimmy Jr. Are you going to the cemetery on Halloween?
第二个问题  你计划几点去
Follow-up question: what time were you planning on going?
因为我也计划那时候去
'Cause I'm planning on going at that time, too.
其他人几点去我就几点去
I'm going when all the other kids are going.
太好啦  太好啦  太好啦
Oh, cool. Cool. Cool. Cool. Cool.
大家为什么非得在可以敲人家门
But why does everybody want to go to a stupid cemetery
要免费糖吃的日子
on a day when you can knock on people's doors
去什么破墓地呢
and they literally hand you free candy?
拿完糖还得亲亲人家的脸蛋
And then you kiss them on both cheeks!
确认一下
So, just to nail this thing down,
我们到时候一起去墓地吗
we're going to the cemetery together?
我去  蒂娜  大家都一起去
Geez, Tina. Everybody's going at the same time.
不是我俩一起
We're not going together.
这是集体活动
It's a group activity.
孩子们一起去探墓
Kids go and break into the mausoleum.
是成人仪式
It's a rite of passage!
那八点半如何
So you think that's, like, 8:30?
要不八点一刻的时候先联系一下
Maybe touch base around 8:15?
能见就见  见不着拉倒
I'll just see you there if I see you.
天呐  他完全被你迷住了
God, he was all over you.
*幽灵和小妖精  小妖精和幽灵*
*Ghosts and goblins, goblins and ghosts, yeah. *
今年我买到了微笑的蝙蝠
This year I got the bats that are smiling.
更像真的
It's more realistic.
为什么微笑的就像真的
Why is it more realistic?
因为它们很开心
'Cause they're happy.
这可是它们最爱的节日
It's their favorite holiday.
它们超爱的
They love it.
你好  我是来除虫的
Hi, I'm the exterminator.
你好  你是"要拥抱不要虫害"的
Oh, hi. From Hugs Not Bugs,
那个有灵异能力的除虫专家吧
the sensitive bug killers.
我们店的名字有误导性
Well, the name is misleading.
事实上我们使用一种剧毒的化学药品
We actually use a highly toxic chemical.
非常缓慢的杀死它们
It hugs them to death, really slowly.
它们会备受折磨  我叫马库斯
They suffer. I'm Marcus.
几天前出现过
They showed up the other day.
我不知道那是什么虫子
I-I don't know what they are.
长得很奇怪
They're weird.
你还好吗
Everything okay?
这可不太妙
This isn't good.
怎么个不妙法
What-what isn't good?
情况很糟糕
This is very bad.
什么很糟糕
What is very bad?
快吓死我了
This is really creeping me out.
你快吓死我了
You're creeping me out.
到底怎么了
What-What's going on here?
鲍鲍  他开始喷药了吗
Bobby! Is he squirting poison?
孩子们刚到家  他们想看看
The kids just got home and they want to watch.
这间地下室
There is definitely an otherworldly presence
绝对有个异界幽灵
in this basement.
-什么  -幽灵
- A what? -A presence.
等等  你是在说"有礼"吗
Wait, are you saying "Presence"?
-幽灵  -有礼
- A presence? - Presents?
我就觉得万圣节也该有礼物
I always thought there should be Halloween presents!
不  不是有礼
No, not presents.
是幽灵
A presence.
鬼魂
A ghost.
这地下室里有个鬼魂
There's a ghost in this basement.
-太好了  -什么  -鬼魂
- Yes! - What? - A ghost?
谁说有鬼魂
Who said "Ghost"?!
我们家有鬼魂
We have a ghost?
天哪  天哪
Oh, my God. Oh, my God!
天哪
Oh, my God.
你们得抓住它并把它处理掉
You need to catch it and get rid of it.
就像抓鲑鱼
Like salmon.
你好  马库斯
Marcus. Hi. Hello.
那么问题来了
Question.
你刚刚是说我们得抓住鬼魂吗
Did you say we have to catch the presence?
-是的  -怎么抓呢
- Yes. - How does one do that?
首先  你们得和它建立联系
First, you got to make contact with the ghost.
然后你们要把它装进一个容器里
Then you got to try to get it into a vessel.
容器
A vessel?
是的  比如一个瓶子  或者盒子
Yeah, like a bottle. Or a box.
-容器  -酷
- Oh, a vessel. - Cool.
你能先灭虫吗
Can you please get rid of the bugs first?
老爸  别说话  装进盒子  然后呢
Dad! So we get it into the box. And then what?
把盒子扔进垃圾桶
Throw away the box in the trash.
很好  现在回到虫子的问题
Great. Now on to the bugs.
你现在能用手里的东西喷它们了吗
Can you just squirt them with your thing now?
不行  那些很可能是被吸引到灵界的
No way. Those are probably phantasmal bugs
幽灵虫子
attracted to the spirit world.
是啊  是啊  幽灵虫子
Sure, sure. Phantasmal bugs.
我可不要下去  我得走了
I'm not going down there. I got to go.
你这算哪门子灭虫专家
You cannot be a real exterminator.
人家有执照的  我先闪了
I'm licensed and I'm running away.
-再见  马库斯  -再见
- Bye, Marcus! - Bye.
我不会付钱的
I'm not paying you for this!
-我去拿通灵板  -还有盒子
- I'll get the Ouija board! - And a box!
-还有蜡烛  -再带张舒缓的爵士乐CD
- And candles! - And some smooth jazz.
餐馆关门了
Well, the restaurant is closed.
谢谢你们一整晚啥忙都没帮上
Thank you so much for not helping out at all tonight.
不客气
You're welcome.
虽然没人关心  我还是要说
I called another exterminator,
我另外找了一个灭虫专家
not that you care.
你们继续
So, yeah, just go ahead,
你们的捉鬼招魂仪式吧
do your capture-the-ghost seance.
这就是我们的容器
All right, so here's our vessel.
这是我的逸致布瑞芝鞋盒
I brought my Easy Breezy shoe box.
它曾经装着这世上最舒服的高跟鞋
It used to hold the world's most comfortable heels.
现在我要用它来装一个幽灵
Now it's gonna hold a ghost.
这个盒子的生命历程还真丰富
What a life this box has had.
好  我们开始吧
Okay. Here we go.
我们要和另一个世界建立联系了
We're gonna make contact with the other side.
让我喝一杯招魂酒先
I just need one more sip of my seance wine. Yep.
如果联系上了
If you make contact,
帮我问问那鬼搞卫生它在行吗
can you ask the ghost if it's any good with a mop?
真有意思  开门
Very funny. Open the door.
注意了  鬼魂
Attention, ghost.
我们今天聚集于此
We are gathered here today
是为了帮你住进这盒子
to help you cross over into this box.
孩子们  把手放这里
Kids, put your hands on the thingy.
第一个问题  这个地下室里有鬼魂吗
Question one: is there a spirit here in this basement?
动了
It's moving!
是
太好了
Great.
这里也有了
They're in here, too.
知道吗
Hey, guess what.
你才不是什么幽灵呢
You're not phantasmal.
你就是个哑巴虫
You're phan-dumb.
天哪
Oh, my God!
你叫什么名字
What is your name?
你叫什么名字  宝贝
What's your name, baby?
别动了  露易丝
Stop moving it, Louise.
我知道是你在动
I know it's you.
我没动  是吉恩动的
I'm not moving it. It's Gene.
不是我
It's not me.
看  拼出字母来了
Look, it's spelling something out.
J
J...
E
E...
F
F...
F.
杰夫  我起鸡皮疙瘩了
Jeff. I just got chills.
杰夫  你多大了
How old are you, Jeff?
1  3
One. Three.
这鬼魂是个13岁的男生
So the ghost is a 13-year-old boy.
挺有意思的  对我们大家来说
That's interesting. To all of us.
杰夫  你想到这个
Jeff, do you, want to check out the inside
很普通的鞋盒里面看看吗
of this totally normal shoe box?
是
我觉得他进去了
I think he's in the box!
-盖子盖上  -好了
- Put the lid on it! - Got it.
喂
Hello?
难道没人听到我呼救吗
Did anybody hear me screaming?
刚有一大群虫子飞到我脸上了
There was a crazy amount of bugs flying at my face.
鲍鲍  别怕
Bobby, calm down.
我们抓到鬼魂了
We caught the ghost.
他叫杰夫
His name is Jeff.
一切正常
Everything is fine.
才不正常呢  琳
Everything is not fine, Lin.
里面已经成虫灾了
We have a horrible bug problem in there,
还有  我受够这抓鬼的把戏了
and I'm sick of all this ghost stuff.
抓鬼已经结束了
Ghost stuff is over.
现在只用举行个仪式把它扔进垃圾桶就好
Now we do the ceremonial throwing it away in the trash.
等等  别啊
No, wait! Don't!
你不能就这么把杰夫扔了
You can't just throw Jeff out.
鬼魂也曾是人
Ghosts were people, too.
万一他是杰夫・布里吉斯[美国男演员]呢
What if it's Jeff Bridges?
那我们可就发了啊
Imagine the money.
蒂娜你在干嘛
Tina, what are you doing?
我要养着杰夫
We're keeping Jeff.
蒂娜  你可以养
You can keep him, Tina,
但是记得每天清理盒子
but you have to empty his box every night!
杰夫  第一天来学校感觉怎么样
So, Jeff, how's your first day at school going?
地狱和蒂娜储物柜的味道  哪个更可怕
Which is worse: purgatory or the smell in Tina's locker?
我的柜子已经没味道了  露易丝
It doesn't smell anymore, Louise;
我把酸奶扔了
I got rid of the yogurt.
你们拿着个鞋盒干嘛
Why do you guys have an Easy Breezy's shoe box?
难道今天是"带老妈的鞋来学校"日吗
I didn't know it was Take Your Mom's Shoes to School Day.
盒子里装的不是鞋  是一个鬼魂
There aren't shoes in this box. It's a ghost.
你骗人
You're totally lying.
骗人对皮肤不好  谢谢
And lying is bad for your skin, thank you.
为啥都在围观这个盒子
Why is everyone looking at a box?
我错过了啥
What am I missing?
我好无聊  快告诉我咋回事
I'm bored. Somebody explain it to me quick!
里面有个鬼魂
It's a ghost.
名叫杰夫
His name is Jeff.
这名字非常虔诚
It's a strong Christian name.
蒂娜  你有个鬼魂么
You have a ghost, Tina?
嗨  小吉米
Hi, Jimmy Jr.
这是杰夫
This is Jeff.
他是个鬼魂  是个男生
He's a ghost, he's a boy,
我们常在一起
and we've been spending a lot of time together.
才没有什么鬼呢
Ghosts aren't real.
没错  死了就死了
Yeah. Death is the end.
-就结束了  -说得对  齐克
- It's final! - That's right, Zeke.
就是这样
Yeah, nothing more!
击个掌
High five!
是吗  看来杰夫
Really? Well, maybe Jeff will have something
有话要说了
to say about that.
有人想和他聊聊吗
Anyone want to talk to him?
-我  -好啊
- I do. - Okay. All right.
大家把手放在通灵板上
Hands on the Ouija board, everybody.
你们可以问他任何关于人死后的问题
You can ask him anything you want about the afterlife.
好吧
All right.
如果你真存在  告诉我们鬼吃什么
If you're real, what do ghosts eat?
在动了
It's moving.
S
S...
O
O...
U
U...
P
P.
汤[soup]  他说得对
Soup! He's right!
肯定是真的
Must be real.
颠覆了我的三观啊
This changes a lot for me. A lot.
齐克  你还好吗
Are you okay, Zeke?
不好  感觉好奇怪
No, this is weird.
齐克改变看法了
Well, Zeke's changed.
下一个到谁
Who's next?
我要问
I have a question.
你活着的时候酷吗
Were you cool when you were alive?
V
V...
E
E...
R
R...
Y
Y.
非常[very]  杰夫非常酷
Very! Jeff is cool!
我还是觉得他不是真的
I-I don't think Jeff is real.
总觉得有什么很可疑
Something smells fishy.
-"你"  -天哪
- "U." - Oh, man.
他反驳你了  他赢了
He got you! Ghost burn.
这一点都不好笑
That's not funny.
杰夫很搞笑诶
Jeff's funny.
-时间到了  -等等
- Time's up everyone. - Wait, wait.
我还有一个问题
One more question.
杰夫  你愿意陪我去教室吗
Hey, Jeff, do you want to walk me to class?
是
不错哦  妹子
You go, girl.
看来他看上你了
He has a creepy crush on you.
好诡异
Weird.
我们还得再找一个灭虫专家
We have to call another exterminator.
不然  "甲壳虫・卡尼沃"
Let's go with... "Beetle Kanevil"?
我们这里灭虫的都什么毛病
What is wrong with the exterminators in our town?
你可以问问他
Why don't you ask him?
马库斯
Marcus!
我只是想带我朋友来看看这地方
I just wanted to show this place to some of my friends.
这是菲尔  这是唐
This is Phil and Don.
-嗨  -什么情况
- Hi. - Wait, what?
他们会去看看
They're gonna check it out.
我先撤了
I'm gonna run away.
-拜拜  马库斯  -祝你们好运
- Bye, Marcus! - Good luck!
希望你们别挂掉
I hope you don't die!
他总这么说
He always says that.
你们要干嘛
What are you doing?
这是什么情况
What's all this?
我已经开始检测到
I'm definitely recording
这里的电磁波动了
some EMF traces in here.
我们很可能有了重大发现
We just might have something substantial on our hands.
你们是超感神探吗
Are you paranormal investigators?
说对了
Guilty.
我叫唐  公司分会副经理
I'm Don, vice president of our local chapter.
这是菲尔
This is Phil.
总经理
He's president.
以绝对优势当选的
Voted in by a landslide.
一共一票  我投的
One vote. It was me.
你不能在这里乱来
you can't do that stuff in here.
我们还做生意呢
This is a business.
看来马库斯告诉你们这里有鬼魂的事了
So, Marcus told you about our ghost.
他叫杰夫
His name is Jeff.
现在过得很好
he's doing great.
我是指适应得很好
I mean, he's adjusting well.
我  鲍勃你觉得他过得
I... Bob, do you think he's...
-还舒服吗  -琳  够了
- comfortable? - Lin, stop.
-没有什么鬼魂  -我去
- There is no ghost. - Oh, boy.
唐  快来看看这个
Don, you're gonna want to take a look at this.
-好的  -这个卡座到处都是
- Okay. This booth is covered
明显的幽灵痕迹
in some serious spectral traces.
-我的仪器快爆表了  -我的也是
- My meter's going crazy. - Mine, too.
当然  也有可能是因为手机的干扰
Of course, it could be cell phone interference.
也可能是收音机  或者微波炉
Or an AM radio. Or a microwave.
但我感觉应该是鬼魂
But I bet it's a ghost.
你听到了吗  鲍勃
You hear that, Bob?
鬼魂
A ghost.
看来我们天生就是干这行的啊
Looks like we got our work cut out for us.
小菲  是时候吃午饭了吧
Phil, you think we should order some lunch?
汉堡  七分熟的
Burger. Medium well.
他真了解自己
Man knows what he wants.
所以才能当上总经理
That's why he's president.
什么情况
What's going on here?
没什么  不用在意他们
Nothing. Don't mind them.
有什么需要的吗
Can I help you?
他们这有个鬼魂
They have a ghost.
我们是来调查的
We're here to investigate.
不  没什么鬼魂
No, there's no ghost.
别听他乱扯
Don't listen to him.
-他是  -亲爱的  这有鬼魂
- He's... - Honey, they have a ghost.
我们就在这吃吧
Let's eat here.
我是说  对啊  我们有鬼魂
I mean, yeah, we have a ghost.
快请进  请坐
Come on in. Sit down.
我们每个卡座都至少有一个
We have at least one in every booth.
杰夫  你很受欢迎诶
Jeff, people are loving you!
蒂娜的小伙伴是学校人气最高的盒子
Tina's hanging out with the most popular box in the school.
我才不在乎他受不受欢迎
I don't even care that he's popular.
对我来说  他只是杰夫
To me, he's just Jeff.
-拜拜  -等等  你去哪
- Bye. - Wait, wait, where are you going?
我准备带杰夫去参观
Oh, I was thinking of showing Jeff
科技馆的蝴蝶
the butterflies at the science center.
你们没兴趣的吧
You guys don't want to come along, do you?
应该没有  好的  拜拜
Probably not. Great. Bye.
杰夫  11点前把我姐送回来
Jeff, you have my sister home by 11:00!
等下  还是9点  中部时间8点
Wait, make that 9:00, 8:00 central!
我和杰夫还要看《厨房噩梦》呢
Jeff and I are gonna watch Kitchen Nightmares.
美国真人秀节目
我们可说好了的
That's gonna be our thing!
每年这时候的蝴蝶最漂亮了
The butterflies are beautiful this time of year.
其他时候  他们都还是毛毛虫
The rest of the time, they're caterpillars.
我们这是在牵手吗
Are we holding hands?
我不太确定
I can't really tell.
杰夫  你会说你只是个盒子  对吗
Jeff, you'd tell me if you were just a box, right?
你就是个盒子  是不是
You're just a box, aren't you?
我居然在和盒子约会  天哪
I'm on a date with a box. Oh, my God.
我和蝴蝶来了个蝴蝶吻
I'm getting butterfly kisses from a butterfly.
是你吗  杰夫
Is it you, Jeff?
你是在给我暗示吗
Is this a sign?
小子  你真的存在啊
Oh, boy. You really are real.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
别  别  别  不准吃蝴蝶
No, no, no. No eating the butterflies!
那盒子里是什么
What is in the box?
杰夫
Jeff.
谁是杰夫
Who's Jeff?
你还真是问倒我们了
You're kind putting us on the spot here.
算是朋友吗
Is he a friend?
还是已经超越了朋友
Is he more than a friend?
我们只想享受当下  不想给对方负担
We're just enjoying it right now without labels.
我以为是什么吃的喝的
Oh. I thought it was food or drink.
参观愉快
Enjoy your visit.
琳  虽然出乎意料
Lin, i never thought I'd say this,
但我还是要说
but I'm glad
多亏那神经病灭虫专家告诉我们这有鬼魂
a crazy exterminator told us we had a ghost.
好日子  事实证明餐馆里有死人的时候
Big day. People like your burgers more
你们的汉堡更受欢迎
when there's a dead person in the restaurant.
好了  各位  我们现在要侦听下
Okay, people. We're gonna listen
次音速的超自然现象
for subsonic metaphysical phenomena now.
所有人请保持绝对安静
We need everybody to be very quiet in here.
除了鬼魂们  你们随意
Except for ghosts. You guys talk it up.
大家好
Hi, everyone!
我  我靠
Oh, my. Oh. Damn it.
我们要事情要宣布
We have an announcement.
我们正式约会了
We're officially dating.
鬼魂男友
Ghost boyfriend!
毕业舞会要记得弄点叮叮当当的链子
You'll have to get some clanking chains for prom.
等等  是有个鬼魂在那容器里吗
Wait. Is there a ghost in that vessel?
你说你俩在约会吗
Did you just say you two were dating?
老爸  别奢望她每次
Dad, you're not gonna like
带回家的男友都让你满意
every guy she brings home.
我监测到强烈的活动信号了
I'm getting some heavy activity.
当然了
Of course you are.
这可是杰夫  他就是这样的
It's Jeff. He's like that.
恭喜了  鲍勃  感觉人不错
Congratulations, Bob. He seems great.
是啊  简直是老爸眼中的完美女婿
Yep. Every father's dream.
他来了
There he is!
学校最酷的小子
Coolest guy in school.
好呀  杰夫
What's up, Jeff?
大家好
Oh, hi, everyone.
我和我男友杰夫正准备
me and my boyfriend Jeff were just looking
吃点午饭
to have a little lunch.
天哪  你刚说男友吗
Oh, my God, did you just say "Boyfriend"?
我说了吗  哦对  我说了
Did I? Oh, yeah, I did.
你俩真般配
You guys are so cute together!
你们是最潮情侣
You're the new "It" couple!
同学们  给他们点空间吧
Whoa, people, give them some space here.
不准照相
No photos!
杰夫和我正准备排队去
Well, Jeff and I are gonna get in line.
天哪  你就不能让他歇歇么
God, just leave him here for a second.
你快把他憋死了  蒂娜
You're smothering him, Tina.
让他喘口气吧
Let him breathe.
他已经在盒子里了
He's already in a box.
让他和我们玩一会儿吧
Yeah, let him hang out with us.
这鬼老弟需要点男生时间  来  杰夫
This ghoul needs some guy time. Come on, Jeff!
我要来抓你了
I'm gonna get ya!
-快来  好嘞  -好吧
- Get over here, all right! - Oh. Uh, okay.
我们先各自做各自的事过会再碰头
We'll do our own thing for a bit and then meet up later.
过会见  杰夫  我已经开始想你了
See you in a few, Jeff. Miss you already.
-快滚出来  快来  -小心点
- Get your ass up here! Come on. - Careful.
我回来了  杰夫
I'm back, Jeff.
希望你喜欢吃热狗
Hope you like hot dogs.
杰夫去哪了
Where did Jeff go?
苔米把芥末弄到杰夫的盒子上了
Tammy got some mustard on Jeff's box,
她拿去洗了
so she went to wash it off.
各位  快进来
You guys, get in here!
我去隔间小便
I went into the stall to go number one,
因为我从来不在学校大便
because I never go number two at school,
甚至从来不大便  因为很恶心
Or at all, because that's gross,
乔丝玲有次就把厕所给堵了
and Jocelyn clogged the toilet that one time.
对不起  乔丝玲
I'm sorry, Jocelyn.
但你们看我出来发现了什么
But look what I found when I came out!
"我要和蒂娜分手
"Tina and I are taking a break.
苔米  你真美
Tammy, you are hot.
做我女朋友吧"
Be my GF."
等下  搞什么
Wait. What?
杰夫约我了
Jeff asked me out!
当然我拒绝了
And of course I said "No"
因为这样对蒂娜太不公平了
'cause that's not fair to Tina.
开玩笑的  我答应了
Just kidding! I said yes!
天哪
Oh, yay! Oh, my God,
你俩真是学校最般配的
you guys are the coolest couple in school!
你们应该在一起
You deserve it.
现在是我有个无形的小男友啦
I guess now I have a hottie without a body.
走吧  杰夫
Come on, Jeff.
虽然没人开口
Nobody's saying it,
但我还是要说杰夫真是个混蛋
but Jeff is a scoundrel!
他只是死了  又没结婚
He's buried, not married!
杰夫居然为了苔米把我甩了
I can't believe Jeff dumped me for Tammy.
杰夫什么时候能在镜子上写字了
Since when can Jeff write on mirrors?
我确定那就是他的笔迹
I'm pretty sure that's his handwriting.
是有点女孩子气  因为他很敏感
It's girly, but it's just 'cause he's sensitive.
女厕所真是好
The girl's bathroom is nice!
每个隔间还有个小小的金属邮箱
Each stall has a tiny metal mailbox.
幸好我随身带了给肯的明信片
I'm glad I was carrying around that postcard for Ken.
这让我怎么
I don't know how I'm gonna make it
撑过今天
through the rest of the day.
行了  蒂娜  快起来
Come on, Tina, get off the floor.
有什么大不了的
What's the big deal?
他根本都
He's not even...
不帅气  以盒子的标准来看
hot... for a box.
我才不在乎
That's not what I care about.
我注重的是内在
I care about what's inside.
另外  我们不晓得你是坐在尿里还是水里
Also, we don't know if that's water or urine you're lying in.
应该是水吧
I think it's just water.
没错  是水
Yeah, water.
不  是尿
No, pee.
蒂娜  他们要用超声波扫描你的盒子
Tina, they're gonna do an ultrasound on your box.
盒子今天没跟我们回家
The box didn't quite make it home with us today.
孩子们  有很多人
Kids, there's a lot of people
都等着看这个盒子
who are very focused on the box.
盒子呢
Where's the box?
他换容器了吗
Did he switch vessels?
不  并没有
No, he didn't switch vessels.
他换女朋友了
He switched girlfriends!
换了一个叫苔米的讨厌的姑娘
To an annoying girl named Tammy!
我讨厌他那张愚蠢的鬼脸
I hate his stupid ghost face!
他甩了你
He dumped you?!
我要杀了他  上次没杀成
I'm gonna kill him. Again.
我就知道会这样
Oh, I knew this would happen.
迟早会这样
Sort of.
鬼也是蛮花心的嘛
Spirit appears to be a bit of a player.
蒂娜会没事的
Tina's gonna be okay.
我给她做了花生酱和果冻
I made her a PB and J.
她说她吃不下  所以我就吃掉了
She said she didn't want it, so I ate it.
她还是很难过  我又做了花生酱和果冻
She was still sad, so I made her another PB and J.
她还是吃不下  所以我又吃了
She didn't want that one either, so I ate it.
总之  蒂娜想自己待一会儿
Anyway, Tina wants to be alone for a little while,
然后我们的花生酱要没了
and we're out of peanut butter.
各位  虽然我不想让你们也伤心
Guys, I hate to break your hearts, too,
但是杰夫不是真的
but Jeff isn't real.
你说啥呢
What are you talking about?
是我在控制通灵板
I was controlling the Ouija Board.
我是在捣乱呢
I was messing with you guys.
这难道不是明摆的事儿吗
Yeah. I thought that was pretty obvious.
我叫他杰夫
I named him Jeff.
这是我能想到的最蠢的鬼魂名字
It's the stupidest name for a ghost I could think of.
当然啦  没错
Of course. Oh, yeah.
我知道杰夫不是真的
I know Jeff's not real.
是露易丝搞的鬼嘛
It was Louise. Sure.
等等  让我捋捋顺
Wait, so let me get this straight.
他不叫杰夫  但他是真的
His name's not Jeff, but he's real.
不  吉恩  根本没有杰夫
No, Gene, there is no Jeff!
我只是开个小玩笑
I just thought it would be funny.
没想到蒂娜会爱上他
I didn't think Tina would fall in love with him.
更没料到
And I definitely didn't think
苔米会和我玩同样的把戏
Tammy was gonna pull the same crap as me
不过她镜子那招更棒
but better with that mirror thing.
我要去告诉蒂娜  跟她道歉
And now I'm gonna go tell Tina and say I'm sorry,
这会成为我们今后回忆的趣事的  对吧
and we're all gonna laugh about this someday, right, guys?
我觉得这主意不咋地
I don't think that's such a good idea.
琳  为啥不好
Lin, why is that not such a good idea?
因为蒂娜现在已经很伤心了
'Cause Tina's already feeling heartbroken right now.
如果我们告诉她这个真相
If we tell her the truth,
她心碎的同时还会觉得自己很蠢
she's gonna feel heartbroken and dumb.
她被一个盒子耍了
She got catfished by a box!
那  不告诉蒂娜
So... I'm not telling Tina?
等着吧  你们明天一起去要糖
You'll see. You'll all go trick-or-treating tomorrow.
到时她就会没事的
She'll be fine.
她会变回正常的小蒂娜
She'll be back to her normal, teeny Tina.
她需要的是牛轧糖
She just needs nougat.
万圣节快乐
Happy Halloween!
我是巫婆
I'm a witch!
服装秀开始啦
Costume fashion show!
快出来  孩子们
Get out here, kids!
现在出场的是吉恩
Here comes Gene!
特纳与霍奇
Turner and Hooch.
汤姆・汉克斯主演电影  又名《福星与福将》
讲述主人公特纳和一只狗霍奇的故事
一半是警犬霍奇  一半是警员特纳
Half dog, half Hanks, all cop!
更像特纳和小可爱
More like Turner and Cute.
过来亲一个
Come here, you!
下一位是露易丝
Oh, here comes Louise.
闪闪的蝎人
Shiny scorpion person.
我是《亡命驾驶》预告片里的瑞恩・高斯林
I'm Ryan Gosling from the major motion picture trailer Drive.
好暴力哦  不过评价很高哦
So violent, but so well-reviewed.
最后一位  蒂娜
And here she is, last but not least, Tina!
扮成一个美丽的四眼姑娘
Dressed as a... pretty glasses girl.
不对  你根本没变装
Wait. You didn't change at all.
我不去要糖了  伙计们
I'm not gonna go trick-or-treating, guys.
什么  不
What? No.
你要去
You should go!
去吃点糖  你需要的
Eat your candy. You need it.
还是不了  我就在家里呆一会儿
Yeah, no, I'm just gonna hang out here for a while.
过会儿可能会去趟墓地
And later, I might stop by the cemetery.
如果这次不去  我可能永远没勇气面对了
If I don't show my face now, I'll never be able to do it.
什么  你为什么要去那儿啊
What? Why would you go there?
苔米会去啊
Tammy's gonna be there.
还有某个纸盒子
And a certain cardboard box.
你们俩去吧  我没事
You guys go ahead without me. I'll be fine.
我就看看其他人过万圣节就好了
I'll just watch other people have fun on Halloween.
那孩子就玩得很开心
That kid's having fun.
还好蒂娜没事
Glad Tina's okay.
该去要糖咯
Time to go trick-or-treating!
开玩笑吗
Are you kidding me?
蒂娜有事
Tina is not okay.
看看她那样
Look at her.
我知道我们该怎么做了
I know what we have to do now.
苔米死定了  我要让她
Tammy's going down, and she's going down
自食其果
with a strong dose of her own medicine.
果是我发明的毒果
Which I invented!
好极了  只有一个建议
Love it. One suggestion.
我们能先玩几小时"不给糖就捣乱"
Can we go trick-or-treating for a couple of hours,
再视情况决定吗
and then see how we feel?
-不行  吉恩  -那能先吃点拉面不
- No, Gene! - Can we just stop for ramen?
好耶
All right!
我们是大孩子了
We're the older kids now!
敢来墓地了
Hanging out in the cemetery!
小伙伴  再过两年我们就要为人父母了
Man, in a few years, we'll be parents!
我也有认真交往的男友了
And I have a serious boyfriend.
那我们是不是该闯进
So, uh, I guess we're supposed to break
这让人毛骨悚然的陵墓了
into that creepy mausoleum, huh?
好完成我们的成人仪式
It's a rite of passage.
我们有鬼同行呢
Hey, we got a ghost with us.
会没事的  对吧
We're good, right?
杰夫  看门人你熟的吧
Jeff, you know the doorman?
-兄弟  -嘿  伙计们
- Oh, man. - Hey, guys.
你俩没资格来这儿
You two have, like, zero out of ten permission to be here.
你们太小了
You're too young.
没错  小宝宝
Yeah, little fetuses.
霍奇  别吵
Hooch, heel!
蒂娜呢  哭得屁股都湿掉了吗
Where's Tina? Crying into her butt?
并没有
No.
我的屁股很干爽  也很强壮
My butt is dry... and strong.
-乖狗狗  -嘿  露易丝
- Good boy. - Hey, Louise.
蒂娜  真高兴你来了
Tina, I'm glad you're here.
等着看好戏吧
You're gonna want to see this.
你们不是去要糖了吗
I thought you guys were gonna go trick-or-treating.
而你们不是打算
And I thought you guys were gonna
到陵墓里面去的吗
actually go into the mausoleum.
我们正要去呢  我们只是
We're going! We're just...
让我们的腿做好准备
we're just getting our legs ready.
看  它们迈出去了
Look, here they go!
-苔米  苔米  -干嘛  干嘛
- Tammy? Tammy? - What? What?
杰夫的前任出现超尴尬的
It's so awkward that Jeff's ex is here.
超尴尬
It's like so...
这气氛太紧张了
You could cut the tension with a knife.
管它呢
No, like, whatever.
我有自信  杰夫早把她忘得一干二净了
I'm so confident, because Jeff is, like, so over her.
动起来  我的腿  很好  动起来
Come on, legs. Good, great, come on.
别停  我允许你抖  但不能临阵退缩
Keep going! You can shake, but you can't quit on me!
我什么都看不见了
I can't see anything!
有人把杰夫从我手里拍掉了
Someone just knocked Jeff out of my hands!
你们都不关心人家
You guys don't even care!
我倒是想关心  但我现在怕死了
I would care, but I'm too scared!
齐克  把成人礼蜡烛点上
Zeke, light the rite of passage candle.
好咧  这我从我爸的按摩浴缸旁拿的
Here you go! I took it from my Dad's Jacuzzi tub.
苔米  你的男友
Here's your boyfriend, Tammy.
掉地上了
I found him on the ground.
你应该小心点
You should really be more careful.
这下好了  他身上有大地的味道了
Great. Now he's got ground on him.
抱歉  蜡烛是薰衣草味的
Sorry the candle smells like lavender.
跟现在的气氛不怎么搭
Kind of changes the vibe a little bit.
是啊  我突然觉得好放松
Yeah. I'm feeling really relaxed all of a sudden.
门自己关上了
The door slammed shut!
-谁去打开它  -锁住了
- Well, somebody open it! - It's locked!
-我打不开  -不要啊
- I can't open it! - No!
别啊
Oh, no.
-蒂娜  再试试  -我撞不开
- Tina, try it again! - I can't budge it.
怎么都打不开
It just won't open.
露易丝  你怎么办到的
Louise, how'd you do that?
不是我  我没计划这个
I didn't. That wasn't part of my plan.
那你到底计划啥了
Well, then what was your plan?
我放了几只地下室的虫子在苔米的盒子里
I put some bugs from the basement in Tammy's box.
-就这样么  -吉恩  你当时也在的
- That's it? - Gene, you were there.
你还帮我抓虫子来的
You helped me get the bugs.
我知道
I know.
我只是以为还有更猛的
I just thought there was gonna be more to it.
不过  好吧  还  还不错
But, yeah, no, it's-it's good.
我滴娘啊
Oh, my God!
各位  来看这个
Guys, look at this!
你们全被诅咒了  准备好
"You are all condemned to eternal damnation
永远和我呆在这里面吧
"In here with me.
我是
"This is...
杰夫
Jeff!"
杰夫把我们关起来了
Jeff trapped us!
不好  杰夫  这样不好
Not cool, Jeff! Not cool.
不要啊  终生诅咒感觉很不好很长
'Oh, no! Eternal damnation sounds bad and long!
终生诅咒是最邪恶的诅咒
It's the worst kind of damnation!
露易丝  这要真不是你干的
If you really aren't doing this, Louise,
霍奇整个人都要不好了
Hooch is gonna have an accident.
我发誓不是我
I swear it's not me.
我就知道我不该要蒂娜的二手幽灵男友的
I knew I shouldn't have taken Tina's spooky seconds!
成功
Got her.
好像有点过了啊
This might have backfired a little bit.
飞到我身上来了  飞到我身上来了
They're on me! They're on me!
听着  听我说
Listen! Listen to me!
我有话要说
I have something to say.
我们并没有永远被困在这儿
We're not trapped in here for eternal damnation.
-那是我写的  -什么
- I wrote that. - What?!
幽灵杰夫是假的  是我妹妹编出来的
Jeff the ghost isn't real. My sister made him up.
-什么  -我的老天爷
- Dude, what?! - Oh, my God.
是我编的  嗨  各位
That was me. Uh, hi, everybody.
虫子也是我放的
The bugs were also me.
我心里有那么一部分早就知道杰夫是假的
Part of me always kind of thought Jeff was fake.
直到昨晚  我亲耳听到我的家人
But then, last night, when I heard my family talking
议论他是假的这个事实
about how fake he was,
我才意识到他绝对是假的
I realized that he definitely was fake.
再说  这也太荒谬了  那就是个盒子
Also, it's crazy. It's a box.
但我们想从杰夫身上得到的东西是真的
But the things we wanted from Jeff were real.
我想有男生关心我
I wanted a boy to pay attention to me
永远陪着我
and never leave my side.
乖乖
Oh, man.
我想相信有来世
I wanted to believe that there's more than this life.
我太想相信了
I wanted to believe so bad.
-没关系的  齐克  -天呐
- It's okay, Zeke. - Oh, God.
我们要学会珍惜当下
It just means take advantage of the here and now.
我知道了  兄弟
Oh, I hear you, man.
我想有人陪我看《厨房噩梦》
And I wanted someone to watch Kitchen Nightmares with.
我喜欢他是因为大家都喜欢他
And I just liked him 'cause everyone else liked him.
我应该学会独立思考了
I need to start thinking for myself,
还是你们觉得这样不好  那我就不改了
unless you guys don't think that's cool. Then I won't.
苔米只是想抢走我身边的人
And Tammy wanted to steal someone away from me
因为她是个讨厌且嫉妒心强的女生
because she's a horrible, jealous girl.
她说得对  苔米最难搞
She's right! Tammy's a handful!
但我们不需要杰夫
But we don't need Jeff.
我们从自己身上就能得到这些东西
We can get these things from ourselves.
我不需要男生来关心我
I don't need a boy to pay attention to me.
我可以自己关心自己
I'll pay attention to myself.
吉恩  一个人看《厨房噩梦》也没什么
And, Gene, it's okay to watch Kitchen Nightmares alone.
我讨人厌嫉妒心强也没什么
And it's okay that I'm jealous and terrible.
-不不  -改改吧
- No, no. - Fix yourself!
我的天啊
Holy crap!
蒂娜  你太棒了
Tina, you're amazing.
真不敢相信你策划了这一切
I can't believe you planned this whole thing.
是你关的门然后假装它被锁上了
You-you shut the door and pretended it was locked.
你提前来这儿在墙上写了那些字
You came here early and wrote this on the wall.
对了  你用什么写的
What'd you use, by the way?
最好别是油漆
Hopefully, not paint.
番茄酱
It's ketchup.
没错
Checks out.
我很抱歉我虚构了一个鬼魂
Listen, I'm really sorry I made up a ghost
让你爱上了他
that you fell in love with.
没事  就当是为以后
It's okay. It was good practice
真的鬼魂的出现做准备吧
for when a real ghost comes along.
你让我过了有史以来最棒的万圣节
Well, you made this the best Halloween ever.
而且还有时间去要糖
And there's still time to go trick-or-treating!
都十点半了  来不及了
It's 10:30. It's too late.
该死  小吉米
Ah, damn it, Jimmy Jr.!
为啥你总是知道时间
Why do you always know the time?!
我戴表了啊
I have a watch.
快  赶去太平洋时区
Quick, to the Pacific time zone!
圣地亚哥这会儿还是万圣节呢
It's still Halloween in San Diego!
说实话  我挺想念杰夫的
I'll be honest. I miss Jeff.
鲍勃  我们已经搜集了很多数据
Well, Bob, we have a lot of data to sift through.
该回实验室去作分析了
We got to get back to the lab.
那你们把账结了吧
Let's, uh, close out your tab here.
你俩吃了11个汉堡
You guys ate, uh, 11 burgers.
都很美味
All delicious.
我们也要跟你算一下费用  鲍勃
We were about to settle the bill with you, too, Bob.
我看看
Let's see.
我们做了贝塔波测试  近紫外光扫描
We did a beta wave test, a black light scan
还有音频谱记录
and an audio spectral recording.
算上这些服务以后
With all these services rendered,
我们应该两清了
looks like it's gonna be a wash.
再见  鲍勃  再见  琳达
Bye, Bob. Bye, Linda.
你们不能走
You can't leave.
你们得给钱啊
You have to pay for your food.
我们不能给你们钱
We can't pay you.
为什么
Why?
要告诉他吗  菲尔
Should we tell him, Phil?
我们已经死了12年了
We've been dead for 12 years.
天呐  他们是鬼魂  鲍鲍
Oh, my God! Bobby, they're ghosts!
-我就知道  -再见
- I knew it. - Bye!
等等  等等  别走
Wait, wait, wait. Wait. Hold on.
小心啊  鲍鲍
Watch out, Bobby!
他们会直接穿过你的
They're gonna walk right through you!
能刷卡吗
Do you take credit cards?
原来不是鬼魂
Oh, they're not ghosts.